coinup.org 2017-05-14

# CoinUp | Get free currency for your games

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to coinup.org website and other related sites and applications owned and operated by Coinup ltd (“Coinup”) (collectively referred to as the "Coinup Sites"). In the event of any inconsistency between this privacy policy and a policy listed on one of the other Web Sites, this policy shall control. 

Coinup may offer programs under which you may have the opportunity to earn points and redeem such points against rewards available on Coinup Sites (“Points Collection Programs”) through your participation in activities (“Activities”) including but not limited to: searching the web, watching videos, answering surveys or watching ads. 

By using Coinup Sites, you agree to this Privacy Policy and acknowledge that all information gathered are essential to ensure Coinup Activities and Point Collection Programs are working properly. 

The use of Coinup Sites and any dispute arising from it is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the Terms of Use. Coinup reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use at any time. In case a material change is made to this Privacy Policy, a prominent notice will be displayed on this page. We encourage you to regularly review the Coinup Privacy Policy and Terms of Use pages. 

Coinup does collect information when you are using a service available on Coinup Sites so Coinup can improve the overall quality and safety of your online experience with Coinup: 

  * You might be asked to share information that identifies you personally including email address, Facebook accounts which can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Such information are for example required to get access to the Point Collection Programs.

  * Coinup gather some information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, referring page, browser user agent, date/time stamp, referring page, cookies and web beacons automatically. Those information are required to optimize the quality of the Activities and of the Point Collection Programs.

  * Coinup may place a text file called "cookie" on your computer when visiting Coinup Sites. Such cookie allows Coinup to improve the quality of the service provided on Coinup Sites, and to store the user preferences and settings. A cookie does not allow Coinup to obtain any information personally identifiable (such as real name or address) unless you have specifically provided such information when using Coinup Sites.

  * The search feature and the video portal can send a request to Coinup servers from time to time. This request could include the keyword query, a video category, all HTTP data transferred automatically by the browser (IP Address, User Agent, Cookies, web beacons). Coinup uses this information in order to properly process the user search or video request and to make our services, Activities and Point Collection Programs more relevant to you./li>   

  * Coinup does not sell, rent or trade any personally identifiable information you provide when using Coinup Sites.

  * Coinup is committed to the data security of its users and takes serious measures to increase the security level of the data collected. 

  * The Coinup Sites contain links to other sites on the Web. Please be aware that the Coinup is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Coinup Sites and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by Coinup Sites.

  * In accordance with Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, Coinup does its best not to request, collect or share personally identifiable information from users under 13 years old. If we are notified of any information collected, we will immediately delete the information from our servers.

If any of the Coinup Sites is sold either all or substantially all of the assets related to Coinup Sites are transferred to another entity, Coinup may transfer all information provided by or collected from you, including personally identifiable information, in order to ensure continuity of the Activities and the Coin Collection Programs. 

We will disclose information, including personally identifiable information, data acquired by cookies, and other data, where required by an interception order or other lawful process. We also reserve the right to disclose such information when we believe, in our sole judgment and to the extent consistent with applicable law, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights or safety of others or to enforce, or protect our rights under, this Agreement. You and Coinup hereto confirm that it is their wish that these Privacy Policy as well as all other documents relating hereto have been and shall be drawn up in the English language only. In case you need information in another language, Coinup will do its best to provide them to you.
